(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-09T23:18:27.694229",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Orpheus, time's a wasting
Show me what you really wanna do!
Tonight, it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing that guitar for me and only me
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can't see what I can see
Get back! Let's try!
掃き溜目で希望を
Finding hope in the garbage heap,
Let's just crash
積み上げていくんだ
We'll keep building it up...
頂から高らかに笑え
Laugh loudly from the summit.
Lose control 美しき理想を
Lose control, beautiful ideals...
Heads will roll 汚してくる野郎は誰だ一体？
Heads will roll, who the hell is trying to tarnish them?
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world that seems meaningless,
偶然を重ねた光
light formed from overlapping coincidences.
脈打つ鼓動
A pulsing heartbeat,
誰にもなれない
becoming no one else...
言葉を紡いでよ
Weave your words.
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
天誅！ 降臨するミライ
Divine retribution! The descending future,
No mercy
見逃しはしない 天誅！
I won't let you escape! Divine retribution!
もうだって
'Cause already,
Show me what I'm supposed to say
What's your problem?
夜を一人
Alone in the night,
私迷う
I lose my way.
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure
There'll be no one to save
巡る巡る
Going round and round,
運命に逆らって
defying fate.
出会い 想いを通わせた
Meeting, sharing our feelings...
Strangers I followed with stars in
So I keep on waiting
Wanting
Faking yours, someone you're not reaching
Longing
I can't be someone else
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark
But still I...
クラクラするでしょ
You're feeling dizzy, right?
クラクラ来るでしょ
It's making you dizzy, right?
Follow follow どこまでも
Follow, follow, wherever we go,
そうでしょう
isn't that right?
Flash bang
In this moment
Never got so far
And knowing if I never try
夢を見るたび
Every time I dream,
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I end up thinking about the meaning of my birth.
あぁ 美しい青い日
Ah, those beautiful blue days.
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
No love
No faith
What's up, all you deadbeats?!
Welcome to Disasterpiece release show!
ようこそ！
Welcome!
たくさん楽しもうね！
Let's have a lot of fun!
Let's go! Come on!
You got eyes and ears, but you don't look or listen!
In other words, you're useless, every last one of ya!
And that's why I'm gonna send you all to hell!
All of humanity!
声援 背負い 颯爽と登場
Shoulder the cheers and make a dashing entrance,
そういうんじゃないねえ
that's not how it goes.
I'm just the type you'd forget, so don't waste your time!
千切れ腐りかけの chain
Torn, rotting chains...
Going insane
Somebody's gotta pay
While I live with the pain
Laugh at me now
I'm the one you can't tame
自作決定 天才ストーリー 現代
Self-proclaimed genius story of modern times
お前が募る場所に
In the place where you gather
花は咲く
flowers bloom
かな
I wonder...
Let's riot!
吐き溜めた Hope
The hope accumulated in a dump
積み上がった夜で
in a night stacked high,
ただ機嫌取ったキャラ
a character just trying to please others,
管理問題
a management problem.
えげつない手で勝負
Competing with dirty tricks,
蹴散らして狂うわ
kicking them aside and going wild.
誰が一体
Who on earth...
...who on earth...
誰だって主張しても
...no matter who makes a claim...
この理想は無理だろうって
...saying this ideal is impossible...
誰が言ったって主張しても
...no matter who says or claims it...
勘違いでござんす
...it's just a misconception.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Come on!
正解と不正解の境だって
Even the boundary between right and wrong...
私により歪んでる
...is distorted by me.
Yo, meaningful problems
that everybody's got 'em
and they can't be satisfied until somebody's at the bottom
So what? You think you're special 'cause you got some grade-A hunger?
Well, you ain't getting any younger
Everything that's left is just trash!
心抱える
Holding onto my heart,
時に魂が
at times, my soul...
叫ぶ
...screams.
飛べない鳥のように
Like a bird that cannot fly,
ひたすらくり返した
I kept repeating over and over.
恐れが通る今すぐに
Fear passes through right now,
どけ！
Out of my way!
Let's riot!
吐き溜めた Hope
The hope accumulated in a dump
積み上がった夜で
in a night stacked high,
ただ機嫌取ったキャラ
a character just trying to please others,
管理問題
a management problem.
えげつない手で勝負
Competing with dirty tricks,
蹴散らして狂うわ
kicking them aside and going wild.
誰が一体
Who on earth...
...who on earth...
誰だって主張しても
...no matter who makes a claim...
この理想は無理だろうって
...saying this ideal is impossible...
誰が言ったって主張しても
...no matter who says or claims it...
勘違いでござんす
...it's just a misconception.
Ah...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
勘違いでござんす
It's just a misconception.
皆さん！
Everyone!
We're just getting started!
始まったね！
It's just begun!
Dead Beats!
Resist and take control!
Like primal waves overflowing!
It's a glorious after-life, right?
Underestimated everywhere I turn!
Take a name, but it doesn't make a difference at all!
Got a million different enemies I can recall!
You walking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall!
Hit a motivation, watch it all burn!
I got to tell ya
I never liked ya
Now why would I lie to ya?
Let me enlighten ya!
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure
There'll be no one to save
Where is your pride, your human will to survive?
Was it just empty words
For your grave?
I reach inside this sound
Now all that remains
Is delusion and decay
Cuz of you, I live this way
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals
We're not equals
You're just confused
Lightning never strikes twice in the same spot
So go ahead and run up on me till you get shot
I see the weapon that you're hiding, come on ready or not
Another life and you would never give a second thought
Thinkin' your pride's different than mine
Ticking all your vital signs off
But we still gotta protect all our friends from our enemies
Wouldn't you agree?
Forged in fires of hell
God can't betray you
If I'm a fallen angel
What does that make you?
I'm not debasing myself
To see the same view
When it's your pride on the line
No one can save you from mine
We're not rivals
We're not equals
Thank you for coming today, everyone! It's over!
It's okay! No, no, no, we're back, we're back. Just some technical difficulties.
Staff-san, the beats! Everyone calm down. It's fine, it's fine. We're- we're okay!
Welcome, welcome!
Hey, you know what? It fits- it fits in the theme of the- the show
Hey, you know what? It fits- it fits in the theme of the show...
that there'd be some technical issues.
So it can't be perfect, right? But I am looking at your comments right now, and thank you, by the way, to Shiori for the raid as well!
Hope the outfit reveal went super good!
Hi, Dead Beats!
Hello!
We're here, we're here! We're finally at the Disasterpiece venue!
And I'm- I'm reading your comments, but there- there might be a little bit of lag, so sorry about that.
And I'm reading your comments, but there might be a little bit of lag, so sorry about that.
Anyway, check it out!
I've got a special- I've got my own special mic that is definitely what I'm using to talk and not the headset!
I've got my own special mic that is definitely what I'm using to talk and not the headset!
Um, but check it out!
I'll- I'll show it- I'll show it to you closer later. I've got- Oh, hello! Liz is here, too! Amazing!
I'll show it to you closer later. I've got- Oh, hello! Liz is here, too! Amazing!
Senpai, woo!
Thank you!
Welcome to Disaster Show, everyone!
Disasterpiece is out at long last! Hurrah!
We did it! We finally got here!
And now, um, I'm gonna do some songs for you guys.
Wow, uh, Aka-Supa, I- I can't read it right now, but I'll have to read them later. Thank you so much!
Wow, uh, Super Chats, I can't read them right now, but I'll have to read them later. Thank you so much!
The new art style is so nice.
This is some Unreal power, Dead Beats!
Unreal power!
Stunning, isn't it? I bet you want to get a closer look, and maybe get some screenshots of Mori Calliope's face.
So let me show you! Staff-san is holding a special camera...
おねがいします Woo!
...please. Woo!
Hey, hey!
Hold on, I think this is my normal hand, oh.
All right.
I'm gonna take some, I'm gonna get some good...
...some good reaction, good reactions for you guys. Hold on a second. Here I go.
Check this... Check this shit out.
Haa!
I'm being silly.
I'm being silly, 'cause I need time to chill right now.
"You sound amazing, Calli." I'm doing my best.
...and the outfit, too. Look at how shiny!
Shiny!
It just... it looks so good. And my face?
My face looks good, too!
Oh gosh, I'm still not used to holding the camera though, so I'm trying to make it perfect.
But I might have to edit things... You might have to edit it later.
Hold on, no, I got this. Okay.
RTX on.
Very realistic. I can wink.
Hold on, here I go.
Wait, hold on, I got...
I suck at this.
That's okay, though. That's okay.
It's fine if it's not perfect.
I think I can wink. Check this out.
がんばれ
Do your best!
Close enough.
It looks good. And look behind us, it's got the track
from the LET'S JUST CRASH MV,
and we've got Challenger's car behind me,
and we've also got King's car as well.
Um, and then... well, you Dead Beats, you're all on your way to the next stage, so you're not there yet.
Um, but let me show you my mic. マイク見せたいから
Um, but let me show you my mic. I wanna show off my mic.
Check it... Check out the mic.
This is the special Mori Calliope mic that was made especially for... Isn't it cool?
Look at how sick.
The red, the roses, I'm obsessed. I'm obsessed with it.
So anyway, that's what's going on. Dead Beats, this is like the actual future of Hololive.
Well, I mean, the technology will only get better and better, so...
Anyway, this is exciting. You guys want to see some more songs?
Also, buy the album!
I'm... I'm all bent out of shape. I feel like MCing, I'm like...
...good when it's an actual live, like in a venue,
but then if it's like this, I screw up a lot, so... Oh well.
New merch? Not nece- Well, I mean this... Oh, you're talking about the mic? You want the mic as merchandise?
I'll think about it.
Not a bad idea. I think P-san's listening to that, so I'll have to talk to her about it later.
Welcome to the future!
Anyway Dead Beats, I gotta do a quick costume change and scene change, so let's get out of here,
and I'll sing some more songs, and meet up with you hither and thither.
That's probably the wrong word to use in that situation, but... Thank you Staff-san.
All right, I'll catch you guys there. Time for a...
変身！
Transform!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
助け合うな
Don't help each other,
物語に勝ち取るは愛
win love in this story.
残像に囚われた
Trapped in afterimages,
絶望を変え シナリオを変え
change despair, change the scenario,
時に止まる 脳を刺す劇薬
a powerful drug piercing a brain frozen in time.
感情はノンフィクションで喜怒哀楽
Emotions are nonfiction, through every twist and turn,
一瞬の対比 さあ一切合切の勝負
a moment of contrast, now an all-or-nothing showdown.
失敗も成功も味わえ
Savor both failure and success,
我ら Gold Unbalance
we are Gold Unbalance.
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world that seems meaningless,
偶然を重ねた光
a light woven from coincidences.
脈打つ鼓動 誰にもなれない
A pulsing heartbeat, unable to become anyone else,
言葉を紡ぐ指先
fingertips weaving words.
運命じゃないよ 小さな勇気と体温
It's not fate, but a little courage and warmth,
強気に研ぎ澄ます
sharpening with boldness.
探そう ２人なら やれるさ
Let's search, together the two of us can do it.
Back to back, no matter what, 絶望も吹き飛ぶような Spot
Back to back, no matter what, a spot to blow away despair.
ドンピシャで刻む 時計の針 飛ばすシャッター
Ticking with perfect precision, clock hands snapping the shutter,
誰にも邪魔できない このルート
no one can interfere with this route.
1と2と3と リードしていくから User
1 and 2 and 3, taking the lead as a user.
ウザいくらい 完璧に解き明かしたら
If I solve it almost annoyingly perfectly,
始まる Loop 輪廻のNight
the loop begins, a night of reincarnation.
ルートは無限に ありふれた道じゃない
The path is infinite, no ordinary road,
選ぶの道を 僕は進むぞ
I will forge ahead on the chosen path.
盛大に笑えばいっそ
Better to just laugh grandly!
才能を運用 描いて
Putting talent to work, drawing it out,
刹那的な 愚者愚者なステア
a fleeting, clumsy steer,
初めての物語を生きていく覚悟を
prepared to live through an unprecedented story.
敗者と勝者のデュエット
A duet of the loser and the winner.
劣等感 弾き出せ 不条理に泣く
Kick out inferiority, crying in absurdity,
振り払え 勝利
shake it off for victory.
筋書きは消えない ２人なら やれるさ
The story won't fade, together the two of us can do it!
割れたんだ デシベル たとえ何千の
The decibels cracked, even across thousands...
逃げ出せ 奪い合えない
Run away, we can't compete with each other.
演算された人生
A calculated life.
絶望も 今日も Let me see your fight back
Even in despair, today as well, let me see your fight back!
どんなったって 何にも変わらないんだって
No matter what happens, they say nothing will change.
ミームされた現実にとらわれて
Trapped in a memetic reality.
This life where we're stuck taking chances
飽き飽きしたんでしょう
you must be sick and tired of it, right?
We're living in a world with no direction
Reach out with our words till we make a connection
Tearing the walls apart, facing it all side by side
Once again, it's us against the world
アンバランスな本能を秘め続けさせて
Keep hiding your unbalanced instincts.
本物の偽物から
From the genuine fakes,
派手に失調 アンバランス
flashily falling out of balance.
踊れ
Dance!
So just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I wanna see
A place in history that's mine, I...
I don't know why we're always side by side, but worlds apart
It's trial by fire, I'm fighting for a place where we can breathe
When spite takes over, I might just take it out on you
'Cause you're too good to be true
Struggling, but carrying on
I'll go where nobody has gone
I'm searching again and again and again
For something only I can do, asking...
Why I can't be someone else?
Despite it all, my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark, but still in my heart
Your words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go, but I can't erase you
I'm following behind, but I won't chase you
I'm swallowing my pride until the time that I can face you
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough, but I'll keep on writing
A story that's evolving from the day that I decided I'm alone
I don't belong anywhere anymore, it was my decision
I'm gonna break down the door to your heart without your permission
There was nothing that could make me stay
Remember it like it was yesterday
Hanging on every word you'd say
What if I'd walked away?
How can I still carry on
Someday when you're finally gone?
I'm searching again and again and again
For something only I can do, the truth is...
I can't be someone else, despite it all
My mind has become my hell with no escape
Or hope in the dark, but still in my heart
My words echo over and over
I'm finally letting go, and you can't erase me
'Cause I'm the only one that could ever replace me
Igniting every line until the time that I can face me
I thought that it was love in the perfect lighting
It's never been enough, but I'll keep on writing
The story that evolved me is the day that I'm deciding I'm alright
So just how far can I go?
I think I already know
That view that I wanna see
I still could make it in time...
あ、みなさん Welcome to the next stage!
Ah, everyone, welcome to the next stage!
パチパチ Thank you for the パチパチパチ
Clapping... Thank you for the applause!
Thank you so much! What did you guys think?
And check it out! We got this outfit! Now I'm being goofy, I'm sorry.
パチパチパチ they said. Thank you so much! Oh, is...
"Clap clap clap," they said. Thank you so much! Oh, is...
Is it out of sync? Sorry if there's like a, again...
Is it out of sync? Sorry if there's, like, again...
Just lag. This very high quality machine we're...
Just lag. This very high-quality machine we're...
broadcast to all of you, so
there might be a bit of lag, but I'm happy that I can read
some of your comments in real time. Thank you so much, you guys!
Makes me very happy. Thank you.
Oh, but we might need to refresh the chat, because
now it has stopped moving. Anyway, in the mean-- oh,
there it goes, there it goes. Oh wow, I think it just exploded when Raora entered the chat, anyway.
Thank you so much, you guys. I hope you guys have been liking the new songs.
"MEMENTO" was one of the new songs that I wrote. I wish I could go
into it in a longer MC or talk more about it, 'cause there's so much I want to say
about that song, um, but it's... oh, hold on,
hold on. I'm frozen in place.
Okay. All right. We're good, we're good.
大丈夫。ごめん。
It's okay. Sorry.
ザ・ワールド！
The World!
No problem, no problem. Here,
for now though, instead of going into talking about the lyrics, which I'll probably do during the next
during the next, during the next stream,
we'll find some time before or after I play a game and then I'll talk about the songs.
Um, until th-- Hang on, hold on a second. You know Kenty couldn't be here
for "Gold Unbalance", but you know
what I've learned from Kenty's song is that fan service is very important.
I used to be really like nervous about doing some fan service and stuff like that, 'cause like I'm an embarrassed person.
But Kenty so easily is just like,
"Oh, like 'chu chu' to the fans, like wink!"
And like, I don't know, he's so good at the fan service, and like,
with no shame whatsoever. I thought to myself, "I need to try and do some of that too."
So... um, I'm gonna do that.
Chu!
Mwah!
I'm probably not very good at it, but... anyway.
Chu!
Mwah!
Hold on, I'll start... Oh no, it's perfect because ザ・ワールド！
Hold on, I'll start... Oh no, it's perfect because "The World!"
ザ・ワールド, it stopped for you! So that you could get a little picture.
"The World", it stopped for you! So that you could get a little picture.
Watch where you're pointing that camera. Hold on a second, I'm not pointing it anywhere suspicious.
What are you talking about?
Can I do... can I do a funny face now?
Waaah!
Haaah!
Oh no...
Anyway,
so here's this outfit,
and it looks so high quality again. Hey, you notice something about the stage?
This is the coin from the beginning of "Gold Unbalance".
Dead Beats luck.
意味なんてないような世界で
In a world that seems to have no meaning...
不確かな物語に
In an uncertain story...
Anyway, so check it out. Hold on.
Look at how cool the stage is, by the way.
Are you checking out the stage? Look at the roses, the moon!
It reminds me of when I debuted from Universal Music Japan,
and I had the moon in the background of... what was it?
I think it was one of my debut albums. So cool. Looking very respectful.
Oh, I know. You don't need to tell me.
I already know.
Of course.
As always. Wish I could put it as high as possible.
Whoa, my eyes are glowing in the darkness.
What about the effects? The effects are also so cool
for this show, I can't believe it. We have some even more amazing stages coming up.
If you guys haven't checked out the album yet, it's full of brand new songs.
Um, one of them I composed myself,
and then all the songs, all the English in my songs is written by me.
Um, except for maybe "Cult Following", and that's it.
Um, but that's in a different album, so it's safe to say
all the English lyrics are my own. And then for Japanese lyrics, I basically tell the lyricist what I want
it to be about and give them like my lyrics too so they know what to write about. But yeah,
so it's full of my thoughts and my feelings. I'm gonna put this one, I really don't need to keep holding this.
It's time I must.
Um, but yeah. It's full of my thoughts
and my feelings about the world and the world around me. And this time it's a bit darker,
a bit more emotional, but you guys know that
I have a lot of emotions inside of me, and
I feel like the best way to deal with those is to put them out in the world
in like a productive way. I love 終電,
in like a productive way. I love "Shuuden",
終電, last train. That's what it means in Japanese.
Shuuden, last train. That's what it means in Japanese.
I can't wait to talk more about that song too. That's also very
close to my heart, that song.
I want to say so much more, but I probably need to wrap it up.
"Amazing as usual." Thank you, that's nice. I dig it. Thank you so much.
"The lyrics are all amazing." Thank you, Dead Beats. I appreciate
I appreciate all of you, thank you.
Well, we have some more to do here, so I can't go on forever.
This is a very long MC. So,
let's do another
変身！ And...
Transform! And...
行こう！
Let's go!
Don't look back, look forward, find something you can move toward
Don't look back, look forward
Don't look back
I've been slipping and falling, kept on looking for something to bring me up
'Cause I'm guessing no such thing as hope
Walk the thin ice in a shattered peace, it's more than a reach
It seems so my chances decrease
If it's a win for the cynical as I adjust my beat
Our ending still is unwritten, I think I'm about to break free
My limits closing around me, the sound is less and less real
Because my heart is beating louder than the fear that I feel
Mind's already made, not afraid of unrealistic dream
Looking for my dream team so I can walk on water
Used to look for perfection, now it's progress
Every due paid part of process
In this moment, maybe I'll last
Not knowing if I'll never try
Changing faces in the backlit moonlight
I can see the stars now
Running through an endless sky
Only one moment for you to live how you want it
Don't look back, look forward
Find something you can move toward
Don't look back
I fight another day, these battles inside and outside
Have all that I wanted, why am I still not satisfied?
Lost taxis and street signs, the city mirroring my mind
Alleyways to level up the effort I put in the fight
Yeah, the world called me, I was always dope, but they were like nah
Now it's up to me to rise, make them little surprised
My mind never slides, always riding high, thrive on this lovely hate
My future is kind
Outrunning all my shadows, still in worn-out shoes
With everything to gain, even more to give up and lose
This time you gotta choose, no excuse, tired of sleeping, gotta move and
Visions of tomorrows that are too good to refuse
Red skies waiting, but I've lost my aim
More things change, the more they stay the same
Burning strife and change
This pain will be my strength
In this moment, maybe I'll last
Not knowing if I'll never try
Changing faces in the backlit moonlight
I can see the stars now
Guiding me to find
For this moment, we're no longer broken
Never leaving love behind
This morning I wake up to the sunlight
Living with resolve now
Running with the fearless drive
Only one moment for you to live how you want it
Don't look back, look forward
Find something you can move toward
Don't look back
晴れ渡った 君がため
Clear skies, all for you
花咲いた 明日は雨
Flowers bloomed, tomorrow it rains
為せば成るんだ 惜しみのない
If you try, you can do it, holding nothing back
Pain 越え on and on 惜しまざる
Overcoming pain, on and on, spare no effort
Machine gun chatter, grab head
読もうとせんのよ 破れんコンセント
You won't even try to read it, an unbreakable outlet
切り開け 拓け 達成 空間 infinity
Carve a path, open it up, space of achievement, infinity
気にしないで 本当に 本当に
Don't worry about it, truly, truly
上昇志向の演出 昇級したって
Staging ambition, even if you get promoted
Shining underneath the blue sky, still choose to sing 'cause I refuse to die
Grit teeth and try to look past the pain
For these flowers are watered in acid rain
Can't change belief that I tried and tried
Make a beautiful scene that I left behind
If I can find a place to rest my mind
I could live with a lifetime
It seems I've lost the song I learned to sing
I got a feeling that I'll still sing anyway
さぁ ろくでなし 未来に no mercy
Come on, good-for-nothing, no mercy for the future
Fade out 乱世 死出の旅
Fade out in troubled times, journey to the afterlife
再生の ID
ID of rebirth
焦げ付くほどの Hold you in my arms
So intense it burns, hold you in my arms
Hello, hello 今宵の daydream
Hello, hello, tonight's daydream
Let's maintain
Passion shot to rap
Had you most online, 年々容量オーバー
Had you most online, capacity overload year after year
混線中断 達成する 成し遂げる
Cross-wires interrupted, achieve and accomplish
Travel, trouble, capital lies
Like a bite of false cause, deep end cats hide their claws
Nobody's ever truly what they seem, with a limelight gleam to conceal the flaws
Can't escape the scrollin' and it takes its toll
A million dead ends, thousand loopin' holes
And did it even matter in the end that I held out?
Sorry I could never be the god of the Soul's degree
So to speak, an island full of ghosts
Living out the role I was told to be
Are we old and free?
In a matter of centuries, wonder if there was a point to me?
Was thinkin' for sure I'd belong on my own
But now that I found a place to belong, people I can't live without
Follow me please, don't doubt, without it all, yeah
暗闇 かねの 描いた So nowhere
Darkened, unbending, drawn so nowhere
途切れ切れのキャッチで 辿れたか
With fragmented reception, did you manage to trace it?
Hello, hello, 宵のインソムニア
Hello, hello, insomniac of the evening
Let's maintain in a world where nothing is certain, except that someday we will say goodbye
I wanna keep my eyes on the sky
裁くみたいな街で
In a city like a judgment
Sorrow, 描く未来の Mercy
Sorrow, mercy in the painted future
消えぬ限界の愛
An unextinguishable limit of love
焦げ付くほどの Hold you, oh, you'll fall
Hold you so tightly it scorches, oh, you'll fall
Hello, hello, 宵のデイドリーマー Let's maintain
Hello, hello, evening daydreamer, let's maintain
Shout, we're changing, cause I jam! 沸き出せ 沸き出せ Jump!
Shout, we're changing, cause I jam! Well up, well up, jump!
沸き出せ S.O.S. Fire!
Well up, S.O.S. Fire!
Ah, yeah, yeah...
皆さん! Whoo!
Everyone! Whoo!
How was that? "Tension" and "Mercy", you know?
Writing that song reminded me, yes, I still can write songs that are extremely difficult to perform live.
Let's go! Some things never change, Deadbeats.
But hey, how about the tech for this concert? Hold on, are you guys seeing this sakura behind me?
Like, the detail... Oh, hold on.
Sorry, again, the sakura tree is very powerful! It's such a big item and so detailed.
Sometimes I stop moving, that's okay, it doesn't matter. Whoo! パチパチパチ!
Sometimes I stop moving, that's okay, it doesn't matter. Whoo! *Clap clap clap*!
That was 1000 out of 10, nailed it, let's go!
ありがとうございます! It is clean! Drink water!
Thank you so much! It is clean! Drink water!
That's a really good idea, hang on.
水、水、水...
Water, water, water...
大丈夫、大丈夫...
I'm okay, I'm okay...
The invisible water!
But I mean, if you guys think back to Phantomime, I see a lot of you guys talking about, "Oh, the production, the quality is so crazy!"
It's very powerful stuff going on around here, and they really knocked it out of the park with this.
I just have so much thanks to give to my staff. Um, be sure, we have a little credit roll at the end that will play, and, you know, that's my staff, and big ups to them.
But remember the Phantomime concert, you guys, that we did the little mini live for the release of Phantomime, which was really cool?
That already had like the echoes of the beginning of even better quality for these shows, right?
Well, can you imagine what the next is gonna look like?
I mean, if this looks like this right now, I mean, can you imagine where we go from here?
I mean, it's just really exciting to think about.
20 years from now, Deadbeats, 20 years from now, who knows?
I probably will be as detailed as that sakura tree, but don't worry, it won't be too much, it'll still feel like me, I'll make sure about that.
This is already kind of toeing the line, I think, but I'd love to move my face a little bit more, and stuff like that.
It would be more dramatic if leaves were scattering around. That's a good point!
However, Deadbeats, you say that, if sakura was falling right now, I think that every PC in this studio would catch on fire!
Great idea, though. じろじろタイム!
Great idea, though. Staring time!
Okay, here we go. Now I'm using this camera again.
Whoa, okay, you guys can get... I'm backin' up, I'm backin' up. A bit of a closer look.
That sakura tree behind, that is... Hold on, I got this.
That is 3D!
They're laughin'! They're laughin' at me! You're laughin' at me! Stop it! Stop!
Someday I'll be able to make an angrier face at you, so get ready for that.
That's another thing to look forward to, Deadbeats, when Mori Calliope can make an angrier face at you.
Talking to you.
Ooh! Check out my nails.
Even cats hide their claws.
Claws!
Hey, this is a cute little screenshot, too.
I heard from my P-san... my P-san showed a little piece of paper to me that said that...
I heard from my producer... my producer showed me a little piece of paper to me that said that...
...#DisasterShow entered... entered the trends in USA!
...#DisasterShow entered... entered the trends in the USA!
Thank you so much for that!
Deadbeats, keep it comin'!
Deadbeats, keep it coming!
And some folks are like, "Mori, I can't believe this is free!"
Of course it's free, 'cause I know that the majority of you guys bought the album, so it might as well be free!
And if you didn't buy it, you've at least been streaming it, so...
...it just feels... it just feels right, I guess, to do...
...what I can to make it worth it to you guys even more. Even more so.
Hi! You guys remember this outfit?
It's a little on the older side, but check it out. You guys remember, right?
From my very first solo show, New Underworld Order.
It's lookin' good, right? I'm lookin' good?
It's looking good, right? I'm looking good?
Hi! Hi!
Trying to get as much camera screen time as I can. "Buy the album, buy the album," say the Deadbeats.
お願いします！
Please support me!
If you could, I'd be very happy. Woah!
This is kind of a cool shot with the sakura.
My eyes are glowing in the darkness. Hey there. Hi!
Whoa!
I'll keep trying to make silly faces, though. That's something that'll never change about me.
This is a screenshot moment!
Whenever it stops, it means it's a screenshot moment! Maybe.
Anyway, it's time to move on because I still have a couple songs to sing for you guys.
I think this one will end up being longer than Phantomime, which is a good thing.
I get to sing even more for you.
What songs will they be? I wonder.
ありがとうございます、スタッフさん！
Thank you so much, staff-san!
And yeah, so I guess it's about time that we move on to the next spot.
Looking good!
Thanks, Deadbeats. You wanna see my high kicks? I've been working on 'em.
おいしょ！
Up we go!
And... おいしょ！
And... Up we go!
My high kicks! おいしょ！
My high kicks! Up we go!
Next year I'm gonna kick even higher, you'll see.
Anyway, that's some randomness right there.
Let's go. Next...
変身！
Transform!
行くぞ！
Let me at 'em!
I put my last delusions behind
Still you're creeping through my thoughts tonight
Now I know it's only skin deep
Drawn like moth to flame inside your heat
Heat
Considered myself fine
But I'm crossing every line
Drunk on love that's not mine
Heaven sent you way too late
Kiss of death and take the bait
Past lives and loaded dice
White lies and alibis
Fingers tracing edge of sin
A medicine I never swallowed right
Still no enemy to fight
Not in this light
Stolen whispers, don't ask and don't tell
Step in my world, welcome to hell
Sinking down in your deep black
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
No love
No faith
Just you and I
Dancing 'til the end of time
Ba-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
End of time, end of time, end of time
I still blame myself for this hate
Shame that overflows...
...and never dissipates
I let words unsaid rot slowly
Tainted and unholy, no, don't say it
Watch
Wait
Cold steel pressed against your neck
End of time, end of time, end of time
One last breath before we die
The sight of you intoxicates
Say your prayers, passed the time to confess
It's a game we never plan on winning
When it takes us to rest
Six feet under, side by side
We fall, we break, we drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
No love, no faith, just you and I
Dancing 'til the end of time
La-la-la-la-la-la-la
Ashes fall from blackened skies, all that's left is you and I
Drunken inside, this love is not mine
End of time, end of time, end of time...
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess, though
My heart's beating to your song
Thinking, "Hurry up, Orpheus, time's a-wasting"
Tell me what you really wanna do
Another late night, aimless dreaming, the day to day starts to call
Still got like a million deadlines, drowning in red wine, my back up against the wall
I got my headphones on, walking home in the dark
Dragging feet like I'm born to lose
'Til somehow they're tapping along to you-know-who's song
A melody I can't refuse
I'm a huge fan of your style, you know my name
Singing out my life, I don't feel the shame, okay?
I know I got a little carried away
But we got music when there's nothing else to say
'Cause in my heart there's a spark when you look this way
Can you hear the sound from the stage when you feel the same?
Now I'm in distress, you got me possessed
I might be obsessed, so let me get a little something off my chest, look
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess, though
My heart's beating to your song
Thinking, "Hurry up, Orpheus, time's a-wasting"
Tell me what you really wanna do
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing that guitar for me and only me
Critics so loud, so predictable
They can't see what I can see, you're gonna wind up a star
Got me dancing so far
This distance gap, my fear, my wonder
I wonder if it's enough
'Cause I'm not lying when I'm implying
You're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional
Oh, baby, this could be real love
Give me one chance and I'll take
Dance the night away
In us, help
Now it's a game that I played before
But with the way the scene changed, there is nothing you can blame me for
I'm talking TV screens, magazines, seen you in a couple dreams
Pictures up on every padded wall and floor
Always talking about no time to desire a lover
So why'd you paint your nails up in my favorite color?
I got an attitude, just when it comes to you
See, our reality is kind of slipping out of tune
I'm never lost in the groove with somebody new
If it's devotion you're after, staying true
So are you noticing me, noticing, you noticing me?
No disillusion, but there's not a lot of guarantee
'Cause in my heart there's a spark when you look this way
Can you hear the sound from the stage when you feel the same?
You're strumming next to me, and I'm in ecstasy
And for the rest of the week, I'm depression free
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess, though
My heart's beating to your song
Thinking, "Hurry up, Orpheus, time's a-wasting"
Tell me what you really wanna do
Tonight it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
So distance is fine as long as you keep playing that guitar
Critics so loud, so predictable
They can't see what I can see, you're gonna wind up a star
Got me dancing so far
This distance gap, my fear, my wonder
I wonder if it's enough
'Cause I'm not lying when I'm implying
You're all that I've been thinking of
Maybe they'll call me delusional
Oh, baby, this could be real love
Give me one chance and I'll take
Dance the night away
Hey! Hey! Come on!
So let's blow this joint, and if the feeling's right
Then we can make a little music of our own tonight, come on!
Hey, hey!
Why you walking away? I got a lot to say
Guess I'll save it for the next one, woo!
I ain't trying to stress you, I must confess, though
My heart's beating to our song
So hear me out, Orpheus, thinking next time
I'll show you what I really wanna do
I'm back, Dead Beats! Where'd the cats go?
Hey, wait a minute, where are the weird cats at?
They were just here a second ago.
Dead Beats, check out what I can do. Hold on. Get ready. Are you ready? Check it out.
I'm obsessed with how this dress moves! Dead Beats!
Wait, let me back up a little bit. Look at how it moves!
Ooh... Ooh, so scandalous.
Ah, don't look.
The physics are crazy.
How about those weird cats, though? Doing the dance...
It was so cute. The creature, nice moves!
Thank you, thank you Deadbeats. Pew pew!
Oh, that was fun. That was fun, Deadbeats. I had such a good time with you guys today.
Actually, I mentioned to you guys my family... My family came to glorious Nippon!
Actually, I mentioned to you guys my family... My family came to glorious Japan!
And actually we kind of celebrated the release together.
I was like, you know, sneaking around some places that were selling the album, and then hearing my own music blasting on the speakers!
They were playing Orpheus, they were playing... Golden Balance, they were playing Let's Just Crash.
And for the first time... ever... Deadbeats, walking around the store, I didn't feel like... embarrassed.
Which is a step in the right direction. I feel like I've been getting better, Deadbeats. I hope it was fun. It was so fun!
Deadbeats, I can't even explain... being able to be so proud and say, 'Look, that's my thing, they're playing my song on the speaker.'
It's so cool. I mean, I went to karaoke with my little sister. She told me that 'die for you' is her favorite song of mine, and ME-TA.
Which made me very happy. Those are Little Sister Reaper's favorites, and I sang it for her and her friends.
Because they really wanted to hear, and they were like, 'Wow, free concert!'
It was really cool. So yeah, there was that. What else did I want to talk about? I don't know, I feel like...
Even today, with today's show, I feel like I'm getting more confident to do more things with my voice, and I can do more things with my voice.
It's still a little rough and unpolished, but like, that's the point of disasterpiece in general, right?
I'm working towards my masterpiece. And maybe... it will take some time to get things exactly the way that I want, maybe I'll never get there, you know?
But I'm doing more with my voice, and even though it's new stuff and it needs polishing, I'm really happy with it.
What's my favorite song? Ask the Deadbeats. Oh, I don't know, I like them for different reasons. The one that maybe I'm proudest of is maybe Rivals & Equals.
Because I still listen to that and I'm like, 'Yeah, that's really good.' But then I also really like Syuuden for the lyrics as well.
Probably my favorite lyrics I've written in a long time. So... Yeah, that's right, that Deadbeat says 'It's about the journey.' Exactly.
Well, I'm running out of time here, so let me get this JiDori camera really quick. Hold on. Ah, yes.
Well, I'm running out of time here, so let me get this selfie camera really quick. Hold on. Ah, yes.
My eyes are glowing in the dark right now because we're in a dark area, but now I'm gonna show you the skirt moving. Let me get on the red.
Can I get on the red? Okay, I'm moving my chest... my chest piece, which is myself, to the red. Look at the skirt!
It's kind of hard to see. Sorry. Sorry! Doing my best over here.
Maybe it's better to view from the other side. So, look, there's the... this is the stage from 'die for you' MV.
And then, you can see if we look this way, it's darkness. And then if we look this way, it's darkness.
But it's still really cool. Whoa, what's that? It kind of looks like the wall that maybe leads to the hospital, I don't know.
Respectfully, of course. Peace! So dark... so dark in here.
Peace, peace. I'll make it work. Hi, hello!
It is I, Mori Calliope, and I just released a new album. It's my best work so far.
And in Japan, we got number one album on the... on iTunes ranking! Yay! For alternative, for alternative music!
So let me see how much further we can push. Last time I checked in US, it was climbing, it was getting high up, but you know, a lot of stiff competition there.
So, it's all good, but all good. If we don't, if we don't reach number one, that's fine.
But I'd love for you guys to keep pushing for me, if you would like to. Spread the word and keep listening in all your favorite places.
Keep enjoying the album, and I will keep making... I'll keep doing stuff that only I can do.
Like writing Mori Calliope lyrics!
So, yeah. I guess that's about it. I want to give a special thanks to Deadbeats, and to Staff-san. いつもありがとうございます。
So, yeah. I guess that's about it. I want to give a special thanks to Deadbeats, and to Staff-san. Thank you very much, as always.
My staff is the best. Please look at the credits so you know who to say thank you to.
Deadbeats... and yeah, post it everywhere. Thank you, thank you Deadbeat. I'm reading y'all's comments to eat the camera?
I think that's a bad idea. I think they'll get mad at me if I do that.
I think it's gonna break things. So anyway, that's the end of the JiDori camera. Anyway, we are back here.
I think it's gonna break things. So anyway, that's the end of the selfie camera. Anyway, we are back here.
My... my
karaoke streams and streams where I'm singing my stuff,
and uh future shows, if there's a song that you really want to hear,
and future shows, if there's a song that you really want to hear,
like I know a lot of you probably wanted to hear Shuuen, for example,
so...
if you want to hear it, you got to stay tuned and come to the next one.
Like I said, life has no encores. So...
what I want you to do now is just rewatch the live.
And then go listen to the music. Links in the description.
Thank you Dead Beats, as always, for cheering for me.
Thank you for supporting what I do.
I'm... strange,
but you know, this is really fun.
I'm glad I get to do this every day,
and I put my whole heart into the new release.
So...
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
We're playing a game.
There's a game stream tomorrow.
See you guys around.
Thanks again, everyone.
I'm your Mori. Hope you'll remember me.
Peace!
Dead Beats!! Much love to you. Thank you for following your (at times) disaster (affectionate) of an oshi. Let's keep chasing our own masterpieces. Even if we're imperfect, even if we fail every time. That is to live, I think. - Calliope Mori!
[Note: Dead Beats!! Much love to you. Thank you for following your (at times) disaster (affectionate) of an oshi. Let's keep chasing our own masterpieces. Even if we're imperfect, even if we fail every time. That is to live, I think. - Calliope Mori!]
Orpheus, time's a-wasting
Show me what you really wanna do!
Tonight, it's my turn to show you how obvious I can be
Sometimes it feels like you're playing that guitar for me and only me
Critics so loud, so predictable, they can't see what I can see
You're gonna wind up a star!
Let's ride!
Get back! Get back!
吐き出すメチャクチャな言葉
Spewing out messy words,
Let's just crash!
刺激的でブッ飛んだ
Exciting and wild,
いただきケセラセラっすか？
Dig in, is it que será, será?
Alright! Lose control!
美しき算段
Beautiful scheme.
ねえ、ようこそ
Hey, welcome...
ね、世界で 理不尽重ねた光
To a world of light layered with absurdity.
脈打つ心 誰にもなれない
A pulsing heart, I can't become anyone else.
言葉を紡いで
Weaving words...
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire
Sorrow, forgotten, 未来の Mercy
Sorrow, forgotten, future's Mercy.
Mercy
色んなことしてみたいサイの目
The roll of the dice, wanting to try all kinds of things.
でもだって
But still,
Tell me what's wrong, I'm not sick
What's your problem?
夜を一人 アタシが迷う
Wandering alone through the night, I lose my way.
When front to front crashes down
When the world caved under my pressure
There'll be no one to save
巡る巡る 運命に抗って
Turning, turning, defying fate,
出会いを 想いを 通わせた
Sharing our encounters and feelings.
Strangers I followed with stars in
So keep on waiting
Wanting
Faking you're someone you're not reaching
Longing
Oh I can't be someone else
Despite it all my mind has become my hell
With no escape or hope in the dark
But still
クラクラするでしょ
Makes your head spin, right?
ほんのほんの毒素
A tiny, tiny bit of toxin,
そうでしょう
Isn't that right?
FLASH BANG!
In this moment
めまいがするわ
I feel so dizzy.
And knowing if I never try
昨日の夢を見る旅
A journey dreaming of yesterday,
生まれた意味を考えてしまうの
I end up thinking about the meaning of my birth.
ああ美しき 青い日
Ah, beautiful blue days...
We fall
We break
We drown in fire
Lost inside this dark desire